sizlopedia.in 2012-03-20

# Privacy-Policy - Sizlopedia

### sizlopedia.in respects your privacy

Any personal information you provide to us including and similar to your name, address, telephone number and e-mail address will not be released, sold, or rented to any entities or individuals outside of sizlopedia.in.

We have a strict no spam policy and do not send you any emails, unless you subscribe to receive email updates.

### Credit card details

sizlopedia.in will never ask for Credit Card details and request that you **_Do Not_** enter it on any of the forms on sizlopedia.in.

### External Sites

sizlopedia.in is not responsible for the content of external Internet sites. You are advised to read the privacy policy of external sites before disclosing any personal information.

### Cookies

A “cookie” is a small data text file that is placed in your browser and allows sizlopedia.in to recognize you each time you visit this site(customization etc). Cookies themselves do not contain any personal information, and sizlopedia.in does not use cookies to collect personal information. Cookies may also be used by 3rd party content providers such as news feeds.

### Google and DoubleClick DART Cookies

  * Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on this site.
  * Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our users based on their visit to this site and other sites on the Internet.
  * Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

### Visitor Tracking

sizlopedia.in makes use of analytical softwares such as Google Analytics for statistical purposes. For the purpose of stats your IP (Internet Protocol) Address, browser, screen resolution, operating system are captured. We at sizlopedia.in use this information only for statistical purpose and do not share it with any third party.

### User Comments

sizlopedia.in allows users to comment on the site. However we hold all rights to accept or reject any comments based on our discretion. While commenting on sizlopedia.in please refrain from using content that is not suitable.

### Remember The Risks Whenever You Use The Internet

While we do our best to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee the security of any information that you transmit to sizlopedia.in and you are solely responsible for maintaining the secrecy of any passwords or other account information. In addition other Internet sites or services that may be accessible through sizlopedia.in have separate data and privacy practices independent of us, and therefore we disclaim any responsibility or liability for their policies or actions.

Please contact those vendors and others directly if you have any questions about their privacy policies.

For any other information please contact us.
